[
  {
    "question": "77 + 32 =",
    "correct": 109,
    "choices": [
      16,
      -82,
      109,
      58
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "83 + 49 =",
    "correct": 132,
    "choices": [
      198,
      132,
      9,
      -49
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "99 + 81 =",
    "correct": 180,
    "choices": [
      175,
      -152,
      47,
      180
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "73 + 64 =",
    "correct": 137,
    "choices": [
      8,
      137,
      -55,
      161
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "45 + 18 =",
    "correct": 63,
    "choices": [
      88,
      63,
      172,
      100
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "43 + 84 =",
    "correct": 127,
    "choices": [
      -5,
      82,
      127,
      -162
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "80 + 12 =",
    "correct": 92,
    "choices": [
      -96,
      166,
      92,
      -124
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "79 + 77 =",
    "correct": 156,
    "choices": [
      156,
      139,
      -19,
      92
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "72 + 96 =",
    "correct": 168,
    "choices": [
      -126,
      168,
      46,
      98
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "12 + 83 =",
    "correct": 95,
    "choices": [
      42,
      179,
      95,
      -75
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "90 + 16 =",
    "correct": 106,
    "choices": [
      106,
      180,
      -144,
      124
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "95 + 71 =",
    "correct": 166,
    "choices": [
      85,
      166,
      -42,
      97
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "81 + 58 =",
    "correct": 139,
    "choices": [
      5,
      139,
      93,
      90
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "26 + 80 =",
    "correct": 106,
    "choices": [
      106,
      189,
      170,
      56
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "47 + 29 =",
    "correct": 76,
    "choices": [
      76,
      -114,
      -45,
      -53
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "26 + 27 =",
    "correct": 53,
    "choices": [
      53,
      141,
      -117,
      17
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "87 + 85 =",
    "correct": 172,
    "choices": [
      172,
      122,
      -7,
      163
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "48 + 79 =",
    "correct": 127,
    "choices": [
      21,
      127,
      -146,
      155
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "53 + 95 =",
    "correct": 148,
    "choices": [
      -169,
      48,
      148,
      197
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "46 + 55 =",
    "correct": 101,
    "choices": [
      -104,
      199,
      141,
      101
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "85 + 22 =",
    "correct": 107,
    "choices": [
      10,
      34,
      107,
      16
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "65 + 24 =",
    "correct": 89,
    "choices": [
      63,
      -158,
      105,
      89
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "26 + 55 =",
    "correct": 81,
    "choices": [
      -189,
      -75,
      -42,
      81
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "92 + 55 =",
    "correct": 147,
    "choices": [
      147,
      -65,
      174,
      -113
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "69 + 95 =",
    "correct": 164,
    "choices": [
      -175,
      140,
      -55,
      164
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "35 + 73 =",
    "correct": 108,
    "choices": [
      188,
      -116,
      108,
      134
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "94 + 29 =",
    "correct": 123,
    "choices": [
      -158,
      -19,
      -153,
      123
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "25 + 50 =",
    "correct": 75,
    "choices": [
      162,
      32,
      -63,
      75
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "32 + 64 =",
    "correct": 96,
    "choices": [
      96,
      -140,
      22,
      24
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "54 + 81 =",
    "correct": 135,
    "choices": [
      57,
      138,
      16,
      135
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "49 + 19 =",
    "correct": 68,
    "choices": [
      68,
      -4,
      -71,
      121
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "21 + 88 =",
    "correct": 109,
    "choices": [
      109,
      137,
      -64,
      166
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "49 + 50 =",
    "correct": 99,
    "choices": [
      61,
      -3,
      56,
      99
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "63 + 44 =",
    "correct": 107,
    "choices": [
      -58,
      102,
      107,
      142
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "65 + 79 =",
    "correct": 144,
    "choices": [
      113,
      144,
      -104,
      -122
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "90 + 37 =",
    "correct": 127,
    "choices": [
      127,
      186,
      134,
      165
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "51 + 31 =",
    "correct": 82,
    "choices": [
      -140,
      -93,
      82,
      168
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "68 + 46 =",
    "correct": 114,
    "choices": [
      -129,
      -107,
      114,
      58
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "37 + 60 =",
    "correct": 97,
    "choices": [
      167,
      97,
      -182,
      22
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "87 + 79 =",
    "correct": 166,
    "choices": [
      127,
      166,
      184,
      24
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "63 + 59 =",
    "correct": 122,
    "choices": [
      122,
      5,
      83,
      40
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "59 + 59 =",
    "correct": 118,
    "choices": [
      -102,
      118,
      75,
      148
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "53 + 19 =",
    "correct": 72,
    "choices": [
      -65,
      72,
      164,
      -108
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "78 + 15 =",
    "correct": 93,
    "choices": [
      47,
      93,
      -81,
      69
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "11 + 38 =",
    "correct": 49,
    "choices": [
      127,
      35,
      131,
      49
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "19 + 60 =",
    "correct": 79,
    "choices": [
      25,
      79,
      75,
      50
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "67 + 47 =",
    "correct": 114,
    "choices": [
      114,
      30,
      -121,
      -174
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "50 + 50 =",
    "correct": 100,
    "choices": [
      -117,
      84,
      -74,
      100
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "16 + 92 =",
    "correct": 108,
    "choices": [
      108,
      -175,
      -1,
      -94
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "34 + 47 =",
    "correct": 81,
    "choices": [
      96,
      -178,
      81,
      -68
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "58 + 14 =",
    "correct": 72,
    "choices": [
      84,
      189,
      142,
      72
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "49 + 84 =",
    "correct": 133,
    "choices": [
      -128,
      79,
      197,
      133
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "18 + 77 =",
    "correct": 95,
    "choices": [
      95,
      -33,
      11,
      22
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "48 + 83 =",
    "correct": 131,
    "choices": [
      -16,
      131,
      -79,
      103
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "16 + 45 =",
    "correct": 61,
    "choices": [
      -98,
      61,
      145,
      -81
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "47 + 64 =",
    "correct": 111,
    "choices": [
      111,
      145,
      -161,
      155
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "69 + 36 =",
    "correct": 105,
    "choices": [
      -149,
      -20,
      -158,
      105
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "99 + 49 =",
    "correct": 148,
    "choices": [
      -169,
      26,
      148,
      -43
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "76 + 74 =",
    "correct": 150,
    "choices": [
      150,
      -111,
      149,
      117
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "95 + 76 =",
    "correct": 171,
    "choices": [
      -19,
      171,
      57,
      -192
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "85 + 50 =",
    "correct": 135,
    "choices": [
      135,
      123,
      36,
      144
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "21 + 17 =",
    "correct": 38,
    "choices": [
      -33,
      38,
      -110,
      -43
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "96 + 45 =",
    "correct": 141,
    "choices": [
      141,
      -111,
      -74,
      172
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "27 + 34 =",
    "correct": 61,
    "choices": [
      175,
      -166,
      185,
      61
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "69 + 16 =",
    "correct": 85,
    "choices": [
      96,
      101,
      85,
      -175
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "19 + 46 =",
    "correct": 65,
    "choices": [
      51,
      -169,
      -76,
      65
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "18 + 59 =",
    "correct": 77,
    "choices": [
      -119,
      77,
      168,
      -183
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "69 + 97 =",
    "correct": 166,
    "choices": [
      21,
      166,
      36,
      -85
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "62 + 50 =",
    "correct": 112,
    "choices": [
      112,
      -133,
      141,
      -53
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "98 + 60 =",
    "correct": 158,
    "choices": [
      158,
      -50,
      100,
      61
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "30 + 77 =",
    "correct": 107,
    "choices": [
      167,
      107,
      131,
      130
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "38 + 46 =",
    "correct": 84,
    "choices": [
      84,
      170,
      -171,
      110
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "39 + 75 =",
    "correct": 114,
    "choices": [
      160,
      -53,
      168,
      114
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "29 + 33 =",
    "correct": 62,
    "choices": [
      141,
      35,
      62,
      -76
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "56 + 81 =",
    "correct": 137,
    "choices": [
      118,
      -172,
      137,
      -31
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "21 + 46 =",
    "correct": 67,
    "choices": [
      37,
      -25,
      67,
      115
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "19 + 54 =",
    "correct": 73,
    "choices": [
      73,
      134,
      -144,
      8
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "16 + 40 =",
    "correct": 56,
    "choices": [
      56,
      -70,
      140,
      -174
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "17 + 40 =",
    "correct": 57,
    "choices": [
      128,
      57,
      183,
      96
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "75 + 22 =",
    "correct": 97,
    "choices": [
      97,
      -100,
      76,
      191
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "87 + 28 =",
    "correct": 115,
    "choices": [
      110,
      7,
      115,
      11
    ]
  }
]
